Guide to the Kevin Kennedy Ephemera and Photographs AIA.063
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Photographs and Photo Negatives, 1916-2008 (inclusive); 1977-2008 (bulk); 21.67 Linear Feet in 20 record cartons
  - Offally Dinner Dance, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Offally & Pat Burke, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Old, 1925-1996 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Old Galway, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Old Negatives, Dunmore, 1940-1960 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Old Ones, 1950-1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Old Photos, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Old Pictures, 1920-1992 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Old Prints, 1960-1990 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Paddy Connell, Longford, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Parade, 1991-2003 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Parade, Brooklyn, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Parade Galway Bishop, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Parade, IRA Mass, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Parade Meeting, Irish Institute Meeting, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Parade Meetngs, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Parade Party Durrows, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Parade Rapid City, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Parade, UIC, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Park, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Pat Burk, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Pat Harvey, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Pat Kennedy Christening, PTAA, SMA, Hosh, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Pat McGowan, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Patrick Farrells Confirmation, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Paul O'Dwyer, 1992-1997 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Paul O'Dwyer, Kathleen Mulvey, Irish Cult Inst, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Peter M., 2007 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Peto Kunana Party, PTAA, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - People 3, undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Pito Kennedy Gray, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Pioneers, 1981-1995 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Pioneers, Farrells, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Pioneers, Father Bart Daly, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Pioneers and Irish Hall of Fame, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Pioneers, K of C, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Pioneers, Men's Assoc, Cavan, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Pioneers, Tom Murray, Tim Kennedy, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - P.J. Harvey, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - P.J. Reilly, Camogie, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Plaza Hotel, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Police, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Police, Co. Tipperary, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Police Ray Powers, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Polish Center Offally, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Pope Central Park, undated (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Post Office, undated (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - President Grant Tomb, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - President of Ireland, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Proff Co. Tippa, Easter Sunday, NY Co. Board AOH, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Proofs, A.O.H. Bronx, Div 7, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Proofs, Kevin's Pictures, Paper, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Proofs, Runners, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Prostiel Film, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - PTAA, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - PTAA, Astorey, Bride Meehan Weddings, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - PTAA, Bank of Ireland, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - PTAA B&W, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - PTAA, Clynton Goare, AOH Div 3L Ladies, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - PTAA, Co. Cavan, Co. Louth, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - PTAA, Co. Louth, Cahalans, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - PTAA, Consulate, Gaelic Park, Co. Tipperary, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - PTAA, Galway Communion Breakfast, St. Stephens, K of C, St. Patricks Party, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - PTAA Mass & Dinner, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - PTAA, Pioneers, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Queens Bus Party, Forrister, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Queens F. Sons, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Queens Friendly Sons, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Queen Hunlby Son, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Queens Sons, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Rapid City Parade, Trashuney Bee, Mary Ann Wilsons, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Ray Kelly, undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - RCA, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Riccardos Tipp, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Rice High School, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Richie O'Shea Irish Store, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Rising Dublin (1916), 1991 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Riverdale, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Riverdale Steak House, Yonkers Raceway, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Rockaway, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Rockaway Beach and Gaelic Park, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Rockaway Beach, Mayo, Tom Smyth, Danny Moloney, 1916 Mass, Clinton, St. Patricks Day Dance, Galway, U.I.C., Easter, 1982-2008 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Rockaway Beach, Mayor Koch, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Rockaway, St. Patrick's Coney Island, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Rockaway, Tommy Smyth Dance, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Roosevelt Hotel & Mayor Ed Koch, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Roscomma, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Roscommon, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Roscommon Cathedral, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Roscommon Dinner Dance, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Rosee O'Grady, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Rosie O'Grady, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Rose of Tralee, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Roy Conlan, A&C Club, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Runners, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - S. Healy, Brooklyn, undated (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - San Salvador Council, undated (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - San Salvador Council, Knight of Columbus, undated (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - S.D. Wedding, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Seamus Healy, Brooklyn, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Season's Greetings, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Shih M. O'Rourke, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Singleton Wedding, Dunmores, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Singleton Wedding, Galway Hurling Dinner, GMA, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Singletons Wedding, Irish People Awards, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Slattery Group, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Sligo, 1991-1997 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Sligo Div 4, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Special, 1950-1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Special Trial Film - New Camera, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - St. Andrew Society Plaza Hotel, AOH Co. Board Assn Breakast, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - St. Barnabas Football, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - St. Brendan, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - St. Brendan's Church, Bronx, Bank of Ireland, Rockaway Beach, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - St. Hommus Church, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - St. Josephs, 1990-1993 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - St. Joseph's Church, 1985-1995 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - St, Joseph's Confirmation, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - St. Laurence Soc., 1997 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - St. Patricks, 1987-2008 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - St. Patricks, 1950s Cars, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - St. Patrick's, K of C, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - St. Patrick's Cathedral, 1991-1994 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - St. Patrick's Cathedral, Hour Children, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - St. Patricks, Galway Mass, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - St. Patrick, Gov Comoe, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - St. Patrick & Mary Lynches, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - St. Patrick's Dance, Crystal Palace Galway, Confirmation, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - St. Patrick's Day, G.M.A., PTAA, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade (feat. Gov. Cuomo), 1988 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, Galway Meeting, Farrells, Pioneers, Brian O'Connor, Calahan's, Northern Ireland Dance, U.I.C., 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - St. Stefans, Feis U.I.C. Assoc, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - St. Stephen's Church, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - St. Thomas, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - St. Thomas Mor, Bog Dance, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - St. Thomas More, 1995, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - St. Thomas More, Louth, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - St. Thomas More, Waldorf Astoria, Cook Guild, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - St. Thomas More Church, 1981, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - St. Thomas More Church, St. Brendan's School, FR Bart Daly MHM, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - St. Thomas More Church & Tipperary Hurlers Dinner, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - St. Thomas More, Mayo Dance, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - South Dakota, 1994, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - T. Crowe, P. Vahore, Gormly, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Tall Ships, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Tara Circle, St. Thomas Church, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Tavern on the Green, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Tavern on the Green, Kenny Lawford, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Tenefly, NJ, A.O.H. AM, A.O.H. Sheridan Center, P.T.A.A., 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Terrance on Park, Dublin, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Terry Connoworth, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Terry Joyce, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Tipp, 1993-1996 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Tipp Dinner Dance Co Carlow, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Tipp, M. Flannery Mass, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Tipp Visitation Church, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Tipperary, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Tipperary Dinner Dance, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Tipperary Hurlers, Galway Hurlers, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Tipperary Hurling, 1992-1997 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Tipperary, Mayo, Brooklyn, St. Thomas More, Galway, 1982-2006 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Tipperary Offally Proof Sheet, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Tom Kennedy's Golf, Farrell's Mass, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Tom Murray Party, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Toney Phelber, Paul O'D, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Toney Philbea, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Tower View Center, AOH, AIMs, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Tower View Center Co. Clarke, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Tower View Center Woodside, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Tower View Center Woodside, U.I.C. Christmas Party, Crystal Palace, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Trashing Bee & Firemen, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Trial Proof, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Tuam, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Tuam, Co. Galway, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Tyler & Anne Bad Linds & Wall Drugs, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - UIC, 1987-1996, 2006-2008 (Box 22, Folder 33-34)
  - UIC, AOH, Div 24, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - UIC Assoc, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - UIC Association, Roscommon E.G.P., 1986 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - UIC, Brooklyn, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - UIC, Brooklyn, P.O'Dwyer, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - UIC, Christmas Party & Galway Party, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - UIC, Consulate, South Dakota, 2000-2007 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - UIC Dinner, 1994-2000 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - UIC Dinner, Brooklyn (Black/White), 1994 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - UIC Dinner Dance, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - UIC & Galway, 1990-1994 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - UIC Galway Hurlers, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - UIC, Mineola, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - UIC, Mineola, Co Mayo, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - UIC, Parade, Carlo, Rose Gaal, GAA, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - UIC Party, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - UIC, Reprints & Tipperary, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - UK Special, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - UN, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - United Irish American Immigration, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - United Irish Counties Dance, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - United Irish Counties, UIC, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Untitled, 1916-2008 (Box 23, Folder 13-36, Box 24, Folder 1-8)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 24, Folder 9-17, Box 25, Folder 1-10)
  - USA, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Van Cortlandt Park, Bellmont Race Track, Irish Festival, 1997
  - Van Cortlandt Park Bronx Camogie, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Various, 1950-1994 (Box 25, Folder 14-15, Box 26, Folder 1-4)
  - Various, undated (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
  - Visitation Bronx, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Waldorf Astoria, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Waldorf Astoria, Cardinal Cook, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Waldorf Astoria, Cardinal O'Connor, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Waldorf Astoria Cook Guild, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Waldorf Astoria NYC, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Wedding, 1988-1994 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Wedding Brennans, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Wedding Galway, Gaelic Park, PTAA, Minor Board, Irish Police, South Dakota, Kennedy, GMA, New Jersey, 1991-2007 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Westchester, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Westchester Irish, Gerry Adams, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - West Hempstead, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - West Meath Dance, Runner Meeting, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - White House, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Wicklow, Various, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Woodside, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Woodside, FR Colan, Gaelic Park, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Yonkers A.I.M.S., 1997 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Yonkers AIMS & Patrick Kennedy, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Yonkers, Golf, UIC, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Yonkers Irish Day in the Bog, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Yonkers Parade, 1993-1994, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Yonkers, Rocleway, Cavan, Echo Sunay, G. Park, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 29)